Jew hater. I'm a Jew hater.
Because I don't want you killing chickens.
Jew hater.
He's running to the activists.
Part 2 of Capra Week in New York City.
And tensions are rising as
they're beginning to slaughter on the streets
on the sidewalk.
Animal cruelty.
What they doing
and they shouldn't be doing that
because if other ethnic groups are doing that
they'd be charged.
The locals don't like it.
The Jews don't like it.
There's no excuse for this.
This is just blatant animal cruelty.
It's an embarrassment to me as a Jewish person.
What I've learned is they don't like me being here.
Everybody knows this man is here
torturing Jews.
I've seen chickens injured and dead
chickens starving for water from
dehydration.
So there's two trucks with dehydrated dying birds in them.
And now they're starting to sharpen
their sacrificial slaughter knives
killing the chickens in traffic cones
to bleed them out.
Some of the chickens are even running for their lives
across the street to the activists for safety.
All I'm doing is documenting
what's happening in plain sight
and asking if God
really wants this.
Jew hater.
I'm a Jew hater.
Hashem said
Yerum Yahu 722
When I called your fathers out of Egypt
I did not command them concerning
burnt offerings or sacrifices.
But this I commanded them.
Obey my voice.
Not sacrifice.
This is not in the Torah.
It is their business.
They should know the truth.
But they should know the truth.
Better than me?
Better than Yerum Yahu?
Jeremiah?
Isaiah?
Hosea?
All of them say no sacrifice.
God does not like blood.
Or violence.
They're killing the chickens.
It's wrong.
Bad.
Bad. Bad news.
It's wrong.
The chickens are crying.
They're even slaughtering
full grown turkeys now
which begs the question, what's the difference
in Christians slaughtering turkeys
in the tune of 30 million in just a few months
for Thanksgiving?